

CONTACT

Warsaw

+48 518 432 557

michalbystryk@gmail.com

michalbystryk.dev

Employee

Private

in <u>michal-bystryk</u>

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JavaScript (ES6+), TypeScript
- React.js, Next.js,
- Unit tests with Vitest, React Testing Library,
- Node.js (Express)
- NoSQL (MongoDB),
- Semantic HTML,
- CSS (Material UI, SASS, Tailwind, RWD),
- Functional and object oriented programming,
- GIT,
- Devtools.

SOFT SKILLS

- English B2,
- Polish Native,
- Willingness to constantly learn new skills,
- Not afraid of taking more responsibility,
- Problem solver,
- · Good communication skills,
- · Proactive,
- · Curious and questioning.

EDUCATION

Poznan University of Technology Mechatronics (BEng) | 10.2019 -02.2023

- Thesis: Project of a 3-axis milling machine for aluminum
- AKAI Member Academic Web Application Research Group

MICHAŁ BYSTRYK

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I'm a frontend developer with 2 years of commercial experience in this field. During this period I've successfully developed scalable and user-friendly applications that helped with achieving the company's business goals. Even though I specialize in frontend, I have also developed some backend for my personal projects so I'm not afraid of touching it.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

SignalOS | 03.2024 - ongoing

React.js, Next.js, React Native, TypeScript, Material UI, Vitest

- Developing admin dashboards, mobile apps and email templates with help of React, React Native and Typescript,
- Writing unit/integration tests using Vitest and React Testing Library,
- Refactoring legacy code,
- Collaborating with Product Owner and Designer to achieve the best possible result.

Frontend Developer

Mobile Marketing Center | 01.2023 - 12.2023

React.js, Redux, TypeScript, Styled Components, SCSS

- Developed application for learning foreign languages with technologies such as React, TypeScript,
- Created responsive and effective websites,
- · Developed custom sales forms' validation,
- Collaborated with a graphic designer to ensure the best UX/UI,
- Developed HTML based emails,
- Optimized sites for performance, SEO, accessibility,
- Integrated websites with analytic tools such as Google Analytics, Hotjar.

LATEST PROJECT (IN PROGRESS)

Admin dashboard | Live demo | Github

- User authentication with Clerk and Next middleware.
- · Light/dark mode,
- Multi-language,
- · Revenue and expenses,
- Users by device,
- · Recent orders.

Tech stack: React 19 (Server components), Next.js, Typescript, MongoDB, Material UI, Zod, Zustand.

AWARDS

AKAI Code 2022 Hackathon

Winners of the "Best use of technology" category

IT-inder - Artificial intelligence and swipe mechanism used to connect developers with projects that match their experience and the technologies used. I was responsible for creating the front end of the application.

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process.